{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733251103","data":{"timestamp":" 947733251102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733260282","data":{"timestamp":" 947733260281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733260504","data":{"timestamp":" 947733260504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733261475","data":{"timestamp":" 947733261475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733262750","data":{"timestamp":" 947733262749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733265665","data":{"timestamp":" 947733265665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733266522","data":{"timestamp":" 947733266521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733266842","data":{"timestamp":" 947733266842"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733268075","data":{"timestamp":" 947733268075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733271648","data":{"timestamp":" 947733271648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733272631","data":{"timestamp":" 947733272631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733272884","data":{"timestamp":" 947733272884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733273828","data":{"timestamp":" 947733273828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733276705","data":{"timestamp":" 947733276704"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733277750","data":{"timestamp":" 947733277750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733278233","data":{"timestamp":" 947733278232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733282785","data":{"timestamp":" 947733282784"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733282890","data":{"timestamp":" 947733282890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733297161","data":{"timestamp":" 947733297161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_60","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733312166","data":{"timestamp":" 947733312166"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3cef1ca0-975b-4a27-99be-0c137bcc9ef5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733680762","data":{"timestamp":" 947733680762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" a74af7ed-5f7f-4d7f-ad5a-0f9d8a039879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733688037","data":{"timestamp":" 947733688037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" a74af7ed-5f7f-4d7f-ad5a-0f9d8a039879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733694549","data":{"timestamp":" 947733694549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" a74af7ed-5f7f-4d7f-ad5a-0f9d8a039879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733704614","data":{"timestamp":" 947733704614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" a74af7ed-5f7f-4d7f-ad5a-0f9d8a039879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733721665","data":{"timestamp":" 947733721665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" a74af7ed-5f7f-4d7f-ad5a-0f9d8a039879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+0"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733732648","data":{"timestamp":" 947733732647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" a74af7ed-5f7f-4d7f-ad5a-0f9d8a039879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733733853","data":{"timestamp":" 947733733853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" a74af7ed-5f7f-4d7f-ad5a-0f9d8a039879"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733748858","data":{"timestamp":" 947733748858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733750440","data":{"timestamp":" 947733750440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733753515","data":{"timestamp":" 947733753515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733754992","data":{"timestamp":" 947733754992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733757552","data":{"timestamp":" 947733757551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733768220","data":{"timestamp":" 947733768219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KILIJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733769887","data":{"timestamp":" 947733769887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733771968","data":{"timestamp":" 947733771967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733774664","data":{"timestamp":" 947733774663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWETU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733776394","data":{"timestamp":" 947733776394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MWETU"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733777873","data":{"timestamp":" 947733777872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWETU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733781652","data":{"timestamp":" 947733781652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733782603","data":{"timestamp":" 947733782603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733785734","data":{"timestamp":" 947733785734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733787439","data":{"timestamp":" 947733787438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733789432","data":{"timestamp":" 947733789432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733791189","data":{"timestamp":" 947733791189"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733793298","data":{"timestamp":" 947733793298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733795335","data":{"timestamp":" 947733795335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733797469","data":{"timestamp":" 947733797469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733799642","data":{"timestamp":" 947733799642"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733802032","data":{"timestamp":" 947733802032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMEJAZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733814585","data":{"timestamp":" 947733814585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733816542","data":{"timestamp":" 947733816542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733818514","data":{"timestamp":" 947733818513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733820459","data":{"timestamp":" 947733820459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733822781","data":{"timestamp":" 947733822780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733824856","data":{"timestamp":" 947733824856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733826938","data":{"timestamp":" 947733826938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733845767","data":{"timestamp":" 947733845767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPAKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733848009","data":{"timestamp":" 947733848008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733852397","data":{"timestamp":" 947733852397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733854465","data":{"timestamp":" 947733854464"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733856520","data":{"timestamp":" 947733856519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733859811","data":{"timestamp":" 947733859811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733868574","data":{"timestamp":" 947733868574"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733871938","data":{"timestamp":" 947733871938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733875047","data":{"timestamp":" 947733875047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIELEKEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733877207","data":{"timestamp":" 947733877207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733879729","data":{"timestamp":" 947733879729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733881049","data":{"timestamp":" 947733881049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733883128","data":{"timestamp":" 947733883128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGHARIBI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733885814","data":{"timestamp":" 947733885814"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733888088","data":{"timestamp":" 947733888088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733890755","data":{"timestamp":" 947733890755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733892481","data":{"timestamp":" 947733892480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733894936","data":{"timestamp":" 947733894936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733896857","data":{"timestamp":" 947733896857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733898744","data":{"timestamp":" 947733898744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733900801","data":{"timestamp":" 947733900801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733912993","data":{"timestamp":" 947733912993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIYOHITAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733918335","data":{"timestamp":" 947733918335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733920152","data":{"timestamp":" 947733920152"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733923293","data":{"timestamp":" 947733923293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAFIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733925492","data":{"timestamp":" 947733925492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733928199","data":{"timestamp":" 947733928199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733928283","data":{"timestamp":" 947733928283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 521fc8b2-3d19-47fe-839f-142895429248"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733946829","data":{"timestamp":" 947733946829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" KITUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733949725","data":{"timestamp":" 947733949725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733950904","data":{"timestamp":" 947733950904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733952557","data":{"timestamp":" 947733952556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" START_MABASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733954705","data":{"timestamp":" 947733954705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733956512","data":{"timestamp":" 947733956511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733958123","data":{"timestamp":" 947733958123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" MWETU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733961730","data":{"timestamp":" 947733961730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733963422","data":{"timestamp":" 947733963422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWETU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733967223","data":{"timestamp":" 947733967223"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733970401","data":{"timestamp":" 947733970400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733975222","data":{"timestamp":" 947733975222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733978132","data":{"timestamp":" 947733978131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733981017","data":{"timestamp":" 947733981015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733984836","data":{"timestamp":" 947733984836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733988806","data":{"timestamp":" 947733988806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733991424","data":{"timestamp":" 947733991424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733993367","data":{"timestamp":" 947733993367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733995658","data":{"timestamp":" 947733995657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIMEJAZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733997677","data":{"timestamp":" 947733997677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947733999617","data":{"timestamp":" 947733999616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734001492","data":{"timestamp":" 947734001492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734003129","data":{"timestamp":" 947734003129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734007504","data":{"timestamp":" 947734007504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734009571","data":{"timestamp":" 947734009571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734012406","data":{"timestamp":" 947734012405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734014742","data":{"timestamp":" 947734014742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chini palikuwa na mizigo zaidi ya kupakia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPAKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734017403","data":{"timestamp":" 947734017402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734022877","data":{"timestamp":" 947734022877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIITA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734025861","data":{"timestamp":" 947734025861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734027802","data":{"timestamp":" 947734027802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734030235","data":{"timestamp":" 947734030235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734032377","data":{"timestamp":" 947734032377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734052014","data":{"timestamp":" 947734052013"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734052017","data":{"timestamp":" 947734052017"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734056329","data":{"timestamp":" 947734056329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIELEKEA"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734067622","data":{"timestamp":" 947734067622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIELEKEA"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734069589","data":{"timestamp":" 947734069589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta waliita majina tofauti ya mahali basi zilielekea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIELEKEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734072730","data":{"timestamp":" 947734072729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734075264","data":{"timestamp":" 947734075264"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734077306","data":{"timestamp":" 947734077305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734079418","data":{"timestamp":" 947734079418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenda magharibi!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGHARIBI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734082682","data":{"timestamp":" 947734082682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILISIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734085334","data":{"timestamp":" 947734085334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734089333","data":{"timestamp":" 947734089333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734090798","data":{"timestamp":" 947734090798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734093622","data":{"timestamp":" 947734093621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilisikia kondakta akiita kwa sauti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734096005","data":{"timestamp":" 947734096005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734097761","data":{"timestamp":" 947734097761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734099882","data":{"timestamp":" 947734099882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734102184","data":{"timestamp":" 947734102184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIYOHITAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734109712","data":{"timestamp":" 947734109712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734115872","data":{"timestamp":" 947734115872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734122739","data":{"timestamp":" 947734122739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" USAFIRI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734125032","data":{"timestamp":" 947734125032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USAFIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734127375","data":{"timestamp":" 947734127375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ndiyo basi niliyohitaji kupanda kwa usafiri wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734128927","data":{"timestamp":" 947734128927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734130502","data":{"timestamp":" 947734130502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734132226","data":{"timestamp":" 947734132225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734134097","data":{"timestamp":" 947734134097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734137839","data":{"timestamp":" 947734137839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734140127","data":{"timestamp":" 947734140127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734142480","data":{"timestamp":" 947734142480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734144619","data":{"timestamp":" 947734144619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734146612","data":{"timestamp":" 947734146612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734149471","data":{"timestamp":" 947734149471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734152532","data":{"timestamp":" 947734152532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIJISHUGHULISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734154915","data":{"timestamp":" 947734154914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734156487","data":{"timestamp":" 947734156487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kwenda jijini lilikuwa karibu kujaa lakini watu zaidi walijishughulisha kutaka kupanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734158496","data":{"timestamp":" 947734158496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734162641","data":{"timestamp":" 947734162641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734164838","data":{"timestamp":" 947734164838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPAKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734167563","data":{"timestamp":" 947734167562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734175431","data":{"timestamp":" 947734175431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734176973","data":{"timestamp":" 947734176973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734182190","data":{"timestamp":" 947734182190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734185080","data":{"timestamp":" 947734185080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734186670","data":{"timestamp":" 947734186670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIWEKA"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734192778","data":{"timestamp":" 947734192778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIWEKA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734194626","data":{"timestamp":" 947734194625"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIIWEKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734197628","data":{"timestamp":" 947734197628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734198581","data":{"timestamp":" 947734198581"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734199920","data":{"timestamp":" 947734199920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" SEHEMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734203513","data":{"timestamp":" 947734203513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734205421","data":{"timestamp":" 947734205420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine waliiweka katika sehemu ya juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734211146","data":{"timestamp":" 947734211146"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734215527","data":{"timestamp":" 947734215527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPYA"," userResponse":" WAPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734219133","data":{"timestamp":" 947734219133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISHIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734222582","data":{"timestamp":" 947734222582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TIKETI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734231236","data":{"timestamp":" 947734231236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" PA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734236258","data":{"timestamp":" 947734236258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734236893","data":{"timestamp":" 947734236893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734237828","data":{"timestamp":" 947734237828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734240363","data":{"timestamp":" 947734240363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734244282","data":{"timestamp":" 947734244282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734245861","data":{"timestamp":" 947734245861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734248116","data":{"timestamp":" 947734248116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Abiria wapya walishika tiketi zao huku wakitafuta mahali pa kukaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734250079","data":{"timestamp":" 947734250078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734252392","data":{"timestamp":" 947734252392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734254006","data":{"timestamp":" 947734254006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734257045","data":{"timestamp":" 947734257045"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734259231","data":{"timestamp":" 947734259231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734263997","data":{"timestamp":" 947734263997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWATAYARISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734282871","data":{"timestamp":" 947734282871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" START_WATOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734284236","data":{"timestamp":" 947734284236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734286451","data":{"timestamp":" 947734286451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734290938","data":{"timestamp":" 947734290938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734292667","data":{"timestamp":" 947734292665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734292968","data":{"timestamp":" 947734292968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734299633","data":{"timestamp":" 947734299633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734299636","data":{"timestamp":" 947734299636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanawake waliokuwa na watoto wadogo waliwatayarisha kwa safari hiyo ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734302160","data":{"timestamp":" 947734302160"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANGALIA"," userResponse":" NAONDOKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734306317","data":{"timestamp":" 947734306317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANGALIA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734308233","data":{"timestamp":" 947734308233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANGALIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734310116","data":{"timestamp":" 947734310116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734316873","data":{"timestamp":" 947734316873"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734317667","data":{"timestamp":" 947734317667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734321562","data":{"timestamp":" 947734321562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAMBUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734323946","data":{"timestamp":" 947734323946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734327742","data":{"timestamp":" 947734327742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734329734","data":{"timestamp":" 947734329734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAONDOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734333024","data":{"timestamp":" 947734333024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734334794","data":{"timestamp":" 947734334794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734337900","data":{"timestamp":" 947734337900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734339637","data":{"timestamp":" 947734339637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734342256","data":{"timestamp":" 947734342256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia nje na kutambua kwamba nilikuwa naondoka kijijini mwangu mahali ambapo nililelewa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILILELEWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734344442","data":{"timestamp":" 947734344442"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734346430","data":{"timestamp":" 947734346430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734349418","data":{"timestamp":" 947734349418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734351736","data":{"timestamp":" 947734351735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734357358","data":{"timestamp":" 947734357357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa naenda katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734358901","data":{"timestamp":" 947734358900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UPAKIAJI"," userResponse":" WAKAWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734359147","data":{"timestamp":" 947734359147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPAKIAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734362064","data":{"timestamp":" 947734362064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734364797","data":{"timestamp":" 947734364796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAMILIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734369055","data":{"timestamp":" 947734369055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734371768","data":{"timestamp":" 947734371768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734376548","data":{"timestamp":" 947734376548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734380355","data":{"timestamp":" 947734380355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upakiaji mizigo ulikamilika na abiria wakawa wameketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEKETI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734382757","data":{"timestamp":" 947734382756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734385274","data":{"timestamp":" 947734385274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIZIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734387638","data":{"timestamp":" 947734387637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSUKUMANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734390410","data":{"timestamp":" 947734390409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734392549","data":{"timestamp":" 947734392549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINGIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734394566","data":{"timestamp":" 947734394566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734396594","data":{"timestamp":" 947734396594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734398419","data":{"timestamp":" 947734398418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734400409","data":{"timestamp":" 947734400409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734402654","data":{"timestamp":" 947734402654"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAUZE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734404718","data":{"timestamp":" 947734404718"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734407251","data":{"timestamp":" 947734407251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734408151","data":{"timestamp":" 947734408151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734410408","data":{"timestamp":" 947734410408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734415387","data":{"timestamp":" 947734415387"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734417784","data":{"timestamp":" 947734417784"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734420302","data":{"timestamp":" 947734420302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734423649","data":{"timestamp":" 947734423649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734426686","data":{"timestamp":" 947734426686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734429690","data":{"timestamp":" 947734429689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734433076","data":{"timestamp":" 947734433076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734437581","data":{"timestamp":" 947734437581"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mmoja alitaja kwa sauti majina ya bidhaa alivyokuwa anauza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAUZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734439829","data":{"timestamp":" 947734439829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734442210","data":{"timestamp":" 947734442210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734445055","data":{"timestamp":" 947734445055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maneno yao yalinifurahisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALINIFURAHISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734447576","data":{"timestamp":" 947734447576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734453538","data":{"timestamp":" 947734453538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734461782","data":{"timestamp":" 947734461782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" START_ABIRIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734465243","data":{"timestamp":" 947734465243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734467181","data":{"timestamp":" 947734467181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALINUNUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734469565","data":{"timestamp":" 947734469565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya abiria walinunua vinywaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734471666","data":{"timestamp":" 947734471665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734474638","data":{"timestamp":" 947734474638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKANUNUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734474800","data":{"timestamp":" 947734474800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAFUNAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734478828","data":{"timestamp":" 947734478828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734480583","data":{"timestamp":" 947734480583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734483065","data":{"timestamp":" 947734483065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734484209","data":{"timestamp":" 947734484209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wakanunua vitafunaji vidogo na kuanza kutafuna."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734487063","data":{"timestamp":" 947734487063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734492899","data":{"timestamp":" 947734492899"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734495837","data":{"timestamp":" 947734495837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FEDHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734497552","data":{"timestamp":" 947734497552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734503321","data":{"timestamp":" 947734503321"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734505488","data":{"timestamp":" 947734505488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAZAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734508864","data":{"timestamp":" 947734508863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasiokuwa na fedha kama mimi walitazama tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734512189","data":{"timestamp":" 947734512189"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHUGHULI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734514512","data":{"timestamp":" 947734514511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734516935","data":{"timestamp":" 947734516935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKATIZWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734519253","data":{"timestamp":" 947734519253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734521254","data":{"timestamp":" 947734521254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734523356","data":{"timestamp":" 947734523356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734525435","data":{"timestamp":" 947734525435"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734527083","data":{"timestamp":" 947734527082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734529312","data":{"timestamp":" 947734529312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734531859","data":{"timestamp":" 947734531859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISHARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734533644","data":{"timestamp":" 947734533644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734536061","data":{"timestamp":" 947734536061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734538084","data":{"timestamp":" 947734538083"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734540585","data":{"timestamp":" 947734540585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Shughuli hizi zilikatizwa kwa mlio wa honi ya basi ishara kwamba tulikuwa tayari kuondoka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734542775","data":{"timestamp":" 947734542775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDAKTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734545746","data":{"timestamp":" 947734545746"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWATAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734548004","data":{"timestamp":" 947734548004"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734550379","data":{"timestamp":" 947734550379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONDOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734552630","data":{"timestamp":" 947734552630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734554389","data":{"timestamp":" 947734554389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734556533","data":{"timestamp":" 947734556533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kondakta aliwataka wachuuzi kuondoka ndani ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734557968","data":{"timestamp":" 947734557968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734558357","data":{"timestamp":" 947734558356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHUUZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734560967","data":{"timestamp":" 947734560966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALISUKUMANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734562507","data":{"timestamp":" 947734562506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734566123","data":{"timestamp":" 947734566123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734567767","data":{"timestamp":" 947734567767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734570006","data":{"timestamp":" 947734570005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734571864","data":{"timestamp":" 947734571864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wachuuzi walisukumana huku wakitafuta njia ya kushuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSHUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734573980","data":{"timestamp":" 947734573980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734575675","data":{"timestamp":" 947734575675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734578172","data":{"timestamp":" 947734578171"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWARUDISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734580071","data":{"timestamp":" 947734580071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734582465","data":{"timestamp":" 947734582465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASALIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734584253","data":{"timestamp":" 947734584253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734587656","data":{"timestamp":" 947734587656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734590512","data":{"timestamp":" 947734590512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine wao waliwarudisha abiria masalio ya hela zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734593399","data":{"timestamp":" 947734593399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734597345","data":{"timestamp":" 947734597345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734597507","data":{"timestamp":" 947734597507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUHUDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734599700","data":{"timestamp":" 947734599700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734611965","data":{"timestamp":" 947734611965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734623458","data":{"timestamp":" 947734623458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734625904","data":{"timestamp":" 947734625904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDHAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734632127","data":{"timestamp":" 947734632127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wengine walifanya juhudi za mwisho kuuza bidhaa zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734636835","data":{"timestamp":" 947734636835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734645683","data":{"timestamp":" 947734645683"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" KITUONI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734646615","data":{"timestamp":" 947734646615"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" START_LILIPOONDOKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734648604","data":{"timestamp":" 947734648604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOONDOKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734652298","data":{"timestamp":" 947734652298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734655727","data":{"timestamp":" 947734655727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILICHUNGULIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734659498","data":{"timestamp":" 947734659497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" NILICHUNGULIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734668893","data":{"timestamp":" 947734668893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi lilipoondoka kituoni nilichungulia dirishani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" DIRISHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734669945","data":{"timestamp":" 947734669945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734673772","data":{"timestamp":" 947734673772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NILIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734675799","data":{"timestamp":" 947734675799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734684337","data":{"timestamp":" 947734684336"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734687627","data":{"timestamp":" 947734687626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINGEWAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734692033","data":{"timestamp":" 947734692033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734700143","data":{"timestamp":" 947734700143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734702632","data":{"timestamp":" 947734702632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734708428","data":{"timestamp":" 947734708428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" MWANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734710651","data":{"timestamp":" 947734710651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilijiuliza ikiwa ningewahi kwenda kijijini mwangu tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734713369","data":{"timestamp":" 947734713368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734714770","data":{"timestamp":" 947734714770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWAZO"," userResponse":" MAWAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734714773","data":{"timestamp":" 947734714773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734722397","data":{"timestamp":" 947734722397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YALIREJEA"," userResponse":" MAWAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734727283","data":{"timestamp":" 947734727283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YALIREJEA"," userResponse":" MAWAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734729327","data":{"timestamp":" 947734729327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIREJEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734733010","data":{"timestamp":" 947734733010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" MAWAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734736611","data":{"timestamp":" 947734736611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mawazo yangu yalirejea nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734738771","data":{"timestamp":" 947734738771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734739838","data":{"timestamp":" 947734739838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734745876","data":{"timestamp":" 947734745876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734749493","data":{"timestamp":" 947734749493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je mamangu atakuwa salama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SALAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734751518","data":{"timestamp":" 947734751518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734752067","data":{"timestamp":" 947734752067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734755345","data":{"timestamp":" 947734755345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734764116","data":{"timestamp":" 947734764116"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734770428","data":{"timestamp":" 947734770427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATALETA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734774258","data":{"timestamp":" 947734774258"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734778920","data":{"timestamp":" 947734778920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je sungura wangu wataleta hela zozote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOZOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734785551","data":{"timestamp":" 947734785551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" MAWAZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734787221","data":{"timestamp":" 947734787221"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734788429","data":{"timestamp":" 947734788428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734789579","data":{"timestamp":" 947734789578"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" ATAKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734794055","data":{"timestamp":" 947734794055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734795841","data":{"timestamp":" 947734795840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" HELA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734798378","data":{"timestamp":" 947734798378"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734802292","data":{"timestamp":" 947734802292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734807660","data":{"timestamp":" 947734807660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYUNYIZIA"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734808897","data":{"timestamp":" 947734808897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYUNYIZIA"," userResponse":" START_KUNYUNYIZIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734810690","data":{"timestamp":" 947734810690"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYUNYIZIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734810851","data":{"timestamp":" 947734810851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734812743","data":{"timestamp":" 947734812742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MICHE"," userResponse":" WATALETA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734819451","data":{"timestamp":" 947734819451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MICHE"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734820893","data":{"timestamp":" 947734820892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MICHE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734822855","data":{"timestamp":" 947734822855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" ATAKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734825366","data":{"timestamp":" 947734825366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734830280","data":{"timestamp":" 947734830279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734843136","data":{"timestamp":" 947734843136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734846494","data":{"timestamp":" 947734846493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je ndugu yangu atakumbuka kunyunyizia maji miche ya miti yangu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734851193","data":{"timestamp":" 947734851192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734853881","data":{"timestamp":" 947734853881"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKARIRI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734856342","data":{"timestamp":" 947734856342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKARIRI"," userResponse":" NILIKARIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734856345","data":{"timestamp":" 947734856345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734867481","data":{"timestamp":" 947734867480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734869742","data":{"timestamp":" 947734869741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" START_ALIISHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734872872","data":{"timestamp":" 947734872871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734876115","data":{"timestamp":" 947734876115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734878939","data":{"timestamp":" 947734878939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734881326","data":{"timestamp":" 947734881326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734883367","data":{"timestamp":" 947734883367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734885475","data":{"timestamp":" 947734885475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani nilikariri jina la mahali mjombangu aliishi katika jiji kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734887468","data":{"timestamp":" 947734887468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734889150","data":{"timestamp":" 947734889150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BADO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734899723","data":{"timestamp":" 947734899722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJISEMEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734908384","data":{"timestamp":" 947734908384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734917744","data":{"timestamp":" 947734917744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPATWA"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734919786","data":{"timestamp":" 947734919786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPATWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734921893","data":{"timestamp":" 947734921893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734928932","data":{"timestamp":" 947734928932"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikuwa bado najisemea wakati nilipatwa na usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734931712","data":{"timestamp":" 947734931712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734932975","data":{"timestamp":" 947734932975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734934875","data":{"timestamp":" 947734934875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734938561","data":{"timestamp":" 947734938560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734942561","data":{"timestamp":" 947734942560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIAMSHWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734945833","data":{"timestamp":" 947734945833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734950134","data":{"timestamp":" 947734950133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734951765","data":{"timestamp":" 947734951764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734955612","data":{"timestamp":" 947734955612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734958067","data":{"timestamp":" 947734958067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ABIRIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734960425","data":{"timestamp":" 947734960424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734964949","data":{"timestamp":" 947734964949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734967138","data":{"timestamp":" 947734967137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734970133","data":{"timestamp":" 947734970132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya saa tisa niliamshwa kwa kelele za kuita abiria waliokwenda katika kijiji changu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734973749","data":{"timestamp":" 947734973749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILICHUKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734977342","data":{"timestamp":" 947734977342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734983086","data":{"timestamp":" 947734983086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734985123","data":{"timestamp":" 947734985123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734991924","data":{"timestamp":" 947734991923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947734994954","data":{"timestamp":" 947734994953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735001626","data":{"timestamp":" 947735001626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735003882","data":{"timestamp":" 947735003881"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735005941","data":{"timestamp":" 947735005941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilichukuwa mfuko wangu mdogo na kuruka nje ya basi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735007781","data":{"timestamp":" 947735007781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735010396","data":{"timestamp":" 947735010396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735014311","data":{"timestamp":" 947735014310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735017794","data":{"timestamp":" 947735017793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735020535","data":{"timestamp":" 947735020535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735024016","data":{"timestamp":" 947735024015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi la kurudi lilikuwa linajaa upesi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735026474","data":{"timestamp":" 947735026473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735033554","data":{"timestamp":" 947735033553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735037284","data":{"timestamp":" 947735037284"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735038731","data":{"timestamp":" 947735038731"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735040541","data":{"timestamp":" 947735040541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735044703","data":{"timestamp":" 947735044702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGEANZA"," userResponse":" LINGEANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735049395","data":{"timestamp":" 947735049395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" START_SAFARI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735051235","data":{"timestamp":" 947735051235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735052941","data":{"timestamp":" 947735052941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFARI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735059598","data":{"timestamp":" 947735059597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735062452","data":{"timestamp":" 947735062452"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735064275","data":{"timestamp":" 947735064275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735065253","data":{"timestamp":" 947735065253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye lingeanza safari ya kwenda mashariki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHARIKI"," userResponse":" MASHARIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735066104","data":{"timestamp":" 947735066104"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735066700","data":{"timestamp":" 947735066700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735069004","data":{"timestamp":" 947735069004"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAANA"," userResponse":" MAANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735075030","data":{"timestamp":" 947735075030"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735077524","data":{"timestamp":" 947735077523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735079923","data":{"timestamp":" 947735079923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735083999","data":{"timestamp":" 947735083999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735085955","data":{"timestamp":" 947735085955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735088005","data":{"timestamp":" 947735088005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735090639","data":{"timestamp":" 947735090639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735092926","data":{"timestamp":" 947735092926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735099703","data":{"timestamp":" 947735099703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735101723","data":{"timestamp":" 947735101723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735101888","data":{"timestamp":" 947735101888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 4615ec1c-335e-4e75-9178-a8f2d4b586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jambo la maana kwangu wakati huo lilikuwa kuanza kutafuta nyumba ya mjombangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMBANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735134552","data":{"timestamp":" 947735134552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" b5507141-7a70-4482-a670-fd4c94a01f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735137409","data":{"timestamp":" 947735137409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" b5507141-7a70-4482-a670-fd4c94a01f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735138600","data":{"timestamp":" 947735138600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" b5507141-7a70-4482-a670-fd4c94a01f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" SHUGHULI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735140756","data":{"timestamp":" 947735140756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" b5507141-7a70-4482-a670-fd4c94a01f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735141380","data":{"timestamp":" 947735141379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" b5507141-7a70-4482-a670-fd4c94a01f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735141523","data":{"timestamp":" 947735141523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" b5507141-7a70-4482-a670-fd4c94a01f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735147341","data":{"timestamp":" 947735147341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" b5507141-7a70-4482-a670-fd4c94a01f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kituo kidogo cha mabasi kijijini mwetu kilijaa shughuli za watu na mabasi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735177807","data":{"timestamp":" 947735177807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735180169","data":{"timestamp":" 947735180169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735183710","data":{"timestamp":" 947735183710"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735185548","data":{"timestamp":" 947735185548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735187883","data":{"timestamp":" 947735187883"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735190046","data":{"timestamp":" 947735190046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735194408","data":{"timestamp":" 947735194408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735196404","data":{"timestamp":" 947735196404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735200370","data":{"timestamp":" 947735200370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735203049","data":{"timestamp":" 947735203048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735228593","data":{"timestamp":" 947735228593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735236365","data":{"timestamp":" 947735236365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" WALIENDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735241945","data":{"timestamp":" 947735241944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735244394","data":{"timestamp":" 947735244394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735245994","data":{"timestamp":" 947735245994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735250520","data":{"timestamp":" 947735250520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735257920","data":{"timestamp":" 947735257920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735260228","data":{"timestamp":" 947735260228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735262390","data":{"timestamp":" 947735262389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa siku yenye joto kwa hivyo walienda mtoni kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGELEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735265569","data":{"timestamp":" 947735265569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735270458","data":{"timestamp":" 947735270458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUSHIANIA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735273597","data":{"timestamp":" 947735273597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUSHIANIA"," userResponse":" START_WAKIRUSHIANIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735275547","data":{"timestamp":" 947735275547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIRUSHIANIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735277831","data":{"timestamp":" 947735277830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735277840","data":{"timestamp":" 947735277840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735277913","data":{"timestamp":" 947735277913"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGELEA"," userResponse":" START_KUOGELEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735278825","data":{"timestamp":" 947735278825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walicheza wakirushiania maji na kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGELEA"," userResponse":" KUOGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735282863","data":{"timestamp":" 947735282863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735284505","data":{"timestamp":" 947735284504"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735284591","data":{"timestamp":" 947735284591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735293392","data":{"timestamp":" 947735293392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735305717","data":{"timestamp":" 947735305717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 7193289b-4a77-418f-84f0-984e5d4fba24"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ghafla waligundua kuwa saa zilikuwa zimeenda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735318579","data":{"timestamp":" 947735318579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735320907","data":{"timestamp":" 947735320907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735322708","data":{"timestamp":" 947735322708"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735324941","data":{"timestamp":" 947735324941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735327591","data":{"timestamp":" 947735327591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735329432","data":{"timestamp":" 947735329432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735353781","data":{"timestamp":" 947735353781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735368453","data":{"timestamp":" 947735368453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735371168","data":{"timestamp":" 947735371167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGAWAJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735375383","data":{"timestamp":" 947735375383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735377409","data":{"timestamp":" 947735377409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735380256","data":{"timestamp":" 947735380256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735383107","data":{"timestamp":" 947735383107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735384866","data":{"timestamp":" 947735384866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735387441","data":{"timestamp":" 947735387440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735389198","data":{"timestamp":" 947735389198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735395205","data":{"timestamp":" 947735395205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735397685","data":{"timestamp":" 947735397685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735402167","data":{"timestamp":" 947735402167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735405103","data":{"timestamp":" 947735405102"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735417924","data":{"timestamp":" 947735417923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735420243","data":{"timestamp":" 947735420243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735423248","data":{"timestamp":" 947735423247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735426269","data":{"timestamp":" 947735426269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735428395","data":{"timestamp":" 947735428395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735430298","data":{"timestamp":" 947735430298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735431898","data":{"timestamp":" 947735431898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735436384","data":{"timestamp":" 947735436384"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735441387","data":{"timestamp":" 947735441387"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735444241","data":{"timestamp":" 947735444241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735446054","data":{"timestamp":" 947735446054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735450650","data":{"timestamp":" 947735450649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735453990","data":{"timestamp":" 947735453990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFAHAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735458471","data":{"timestamp":" 947735458471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735461415","data":{"timestamp":" 947735461415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735463294","data":{"timestamp":" 947735463294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735466589","data":{"timestamp":" 947735466588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735468815","data":{"timestamp":" 947735468815"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735470894","data":{"timestamp":" 947735470893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735474079","data":{"timestamp":" 947735474078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735476930","data":{"timestamp":" 947735476930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEUPE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735479798","data":{"timestamp":" 947735479796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735482547","data":{"timestamp":" 947735482547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735484703","data":{"timestamp":" 947735484702"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735487937","data":{"timestamp":" 947735487936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735495061","data":{"timestamp":" 947735495061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735497152","data":{"timestamp":" 947735497152"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735500672","data":{"timestamp":" 947735500672"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735510069","data":{"timestamp":" 947735510068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735513444","data":{"timestamp":" 947735513444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735515837","data":{"timestamp":" 947735515837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735517688","data":{"timestamp":" 947735517688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735519918","data":{"timestamp":" 947735519918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735521970","data":{"timestamp":" 947735521969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735523990","data":{"timestamp":" 947735523990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INALIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735528634","data":{"timestamp":" 947735528633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735531181","data":{"timestamp":" 947735531181"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPORUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735534020","data":{"timestamp":" 947735534020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735536343","data":{"timestamp":" 947735536343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735538454","data":{"timestamp":" 947735538454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735540280","data":{"timestamp":" 947735540279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735542514","data":{"timestamp":" 947735542512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735544731","data":{"timestamp":" 947735544730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735549496","data":{"timestamp":" 947735549496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735552276","data":{"timestamp":" 947735552276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735555373","data":{"timestamp":" 947735555373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMENIBANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735559090","data":{"timestamp":" 947735559090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735564134","data":{"timestamp":" 947735564134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735566270","data":{"timestamp":" 947735566269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735567929","data":{"timestamp":" 947735567929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735571037","data":{"timestamp":" 947735571036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735574017","data":{"timestamp":" 947735574016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735576494","data":{"timestamp":" 947735576493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735578746","data":{"timestamp":" 947735578745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735581490","data":{"timestamp":" 947735581489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735584313","data":{"timestamp":" 947735584312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735586264","data":{"timestamp":" 947735586264"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735588556","data":{"timestamp":" 947735588556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735590853","data":{"timestamp":" 947735590852"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735592792","data":{"timestamp":" 947735592792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735594592","data":{"timestamp":" 947735594591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735597080","data":{"timestamp":" 947735597079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735601637","data":{"timestamp":" 947735601637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735606111","data":{"timestamp":" 947735606111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735611659","data":{"timestamp":" 947735611659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735614440","data":{"timestamp":" 947735614440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735616351","data":{"timestamp":" 947735616351"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735621179","data":{"timestamp":" 947735621178"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735624448","data":{"timestamp":" 947735624447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAIPATAJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735627099","data":{"timestamp":" 947735627099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735629068","data":{"timestamp":" 947735629068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735631906","data":{"timestamp":" 947735631906"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735634748","data":{"timestamp":" 947735634748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735642853","data":{"timestamp":" 947735642852"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735645208","data":{"timestamp":" 947735645208"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735647162","data":{"timestamp":" 947735647162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735652929","data":{"timestamp":" 947735652929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIRUKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735655404","data":{"timestamp":" 947735655404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735657898","data":{"timestamp":" 947735657898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735663788","data":{"timestamp":" 947735663787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735665858","data":{"timestamp":" 947735665858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735667991","data":{"timestamp":" 947735667991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOPESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735669781","data":{"timestamp":" 947735669781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735671682","data":{"timestamp":" 947735671682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735673722","data":{"timestamp":" 947735673722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIWEZE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735688046","data":{"timestamp":" 947735688045"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947735690097","data":{"timestamp":" 947735690097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947736093554","data":{"timestamp":" 947736093554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947736140253","data":{"timestamp":" 947736140253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947736228857","data":{"timestamp":" 947736228857"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947736234984","data":{"timestamp":" 947736234984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947736236312","data":{"timestamp":" 947736236312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947736239569","data":{"timestamp":" 947736239569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947736246594","data":{"timestamp":" 947736246594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947736248167","data":{"timestamp":" 947736248167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947736251320","data":{"timestamp":" 947736251320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947736478371","data":{"timestamp":" 947736478371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947736478374","data":{"timestamp":" 947736478374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947737643587","data":{"timestamp":" 947737643587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947737649564","data":{"timestamp":" 947737649564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947737651274","data":{"timestamp":" 947737651274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947737658541","data":{"timestamp":" 947737658541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947737670095","data":{"timestamp":" 947737670095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947737853603","data":{"timestamp":" 947737853603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947737854126","data":{"timestamp":" 947737854126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947737855413","data":{"timestamp":" 947737855413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKARIMU"," userResponse":" UKARIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947737866274","data":{"timestamp":" 947737866274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947737866285","data":{"timestamp":" 947737866285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947737866295","data":{"timestamp":" 947737866295"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947737874623","data":{"timestamp":" 947737874623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_061354"," gameId":" 3b2b2b16-e9e5-45d5-8826-c3457796b4c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}